{
    "id": "d704fa72739d4240a89e3f8bb2a3db9a",
    "title": "Structures with Wish | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "232668e9342f4e70b43e34411820b8fa",
            "title": "Structures with Wish | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ............................ run faster.",
                    "description": "When 'wish' is used to talk about unreal or impossible situations, we use a past tense to refer to the present. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ............................. stay out of this.",
                    "description": "When 'wish' is used to talk about unreal or impossible situations, we use a past tense to refer to the present. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ........................ keep the volume down.",
                    "description": "To express regret that things are not different, we use a past tense with wish. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "will",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ............................... that offer.",
                    "description": "Past perfect tenses are used to talk about wishes about the past. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't accept",
                        "didn't accept",
                        "hadn't accepted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ........................... better looking.",
                    "description": "Was and were are both possible when we talk about unreal situations and conditions. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ......................... take a holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "could",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don't you wish you ........................... fly?",
                    "description": "After wish, we use could to talk about wishes that we cannot realize. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish ........................... a table.",
                    "description": "Wish + to-infinitive means want. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "reserve",
                        "to reserve",
                        "seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you wish .......................... drinks on the terrace?",
                    "description": "After wish, we can use an object + to-infinitive.",
                    "answers": [
                        "I to serve",
                        "me to serve",
                        "me serving",
                        "me serve"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................... an appointment with the manager.",
                    "description": "Wish + direct object is not normally possible without a following infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wish",
                        "want",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .......................... you feel better tomorrow.",
                    "description": "Wish + that-clause is not generally used for wishes about things that seem possible in the future. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hope",
                        "wish",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Now I wish I ................................ to university.",
                    "description": "Past perfect tenses are used for wishes about the past. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "went",
                        "go",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}